Total Experience: 8 Year(s) 0 Month(s)

Highest Degree: B.Tech/B.E. [electronics and

Notice Period: 15 Days or less

instrumentation]



Oracle ERP QA consultant Development, Application Programming, Software Testing, Defect Management, Manual Testing, Functional Testing, Integration Testing, Test Case Execution, Business Analysis, Requirement Gathering, Production Support



Current Designation: Associate

Current Company: CTS

Current Location: Chennai

Pref. Location: Bengaluru / Bangalore, Chennai, Hyderabad Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming /

Maintenance

Role: Software Developer

Industry: IT-Software/Software Services

Marital Status: Married

Key Skills: Associate - IT,Software Developer,Software Development,Application Programming,Software Testing,Defect Management,Manual Testing,Functional Testing,Integration Testing,Test Case Execution,Business Analysis,Requirement

Gathering, Production Support

Verified: Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 20-Jan-21 Last Modified: 20-Jan-21

Summary

8 Years of Professional experience in Oracle Applications Finance modules (AP,AR,GL) ,Oracle Trade management, Oracle Credit management and AR advanced collections.

Experienced in Oracle Applications Implementation, R12 Upgrade, Functional testing, production support and maintenance of Oracle Apps in Finance Modules.

Good Exposure in AP, AR and GL and functional setups

Have Strong Knowledge in Account payables and Account Receivables

Capable of Mapping Business/ Finance processes to system functionalities

 $\label{lem:experience} \mbox{Experience in programming with Oracle tools such as Reports 10g, PL/SQL, SQL, SQL*Loader.}$

Experience in providing functional solutions to the problems and functional guidance to the team.

Comprehensive experience in analysis, design, testing the business systems involving Oracle Applications.

Involved in different phases of Software Testing Life Cycle like Test Design, Test Execution, and Defect Management.

Work Experience

CTS as Associate
Feb 2019 to Till Date

Cognizant Technologies Solutions as Associate Feb 2019 to Jun 2020

Cognizant Technologies Solutions as Associate Feb 2019 to Feb 2019

Wipro Technologies as Associate Consultant Nov 2010 to Jul 2017

Education

UG: B.Tech/B.E. (electronics and instrumentation) from Vivekananda College of Engineering in 2010

Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
French				
English				
Tamil				

Affirmative Action

Category: General

Job Type: Permanent

Physically Challenged: No

Employment Status: Full time

Work Authorization